<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[thenetswatch]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[thenetswatch]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/thenetswatch/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Aug 2016 09:55:10 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/thenetswatch/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA['Bike to the Future': Design Museum Gent considers a world of two-wheeled design.]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>'Bike to the Future': Design Museum Gent considers a world of two-wheeled design.</h1><p>'Bike to the Future' is the latest testament to a cycling revolution we've been witnessing since the 1960s. But the Design Museum Gent isn't interested in the past; between 25 March - 23 October it showcases a collection of contemporary models from the new millennium, including Philippe Starck's electric bike 'MASS' or Tobias Knockaert's laser-cut bicycle, and prototypes and experiments for the future, with unusual aesthetics, materials and functions.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/e75dd9b06e93c20d73aed8ffe8845b13b5208794.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.wallpaper.com/design/cycling-our-way-to-the-future</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">f624be2d-42d2-437b-8a4e-b5be2d180f67</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Aug 2016 09:55:05 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Ars VR headset showdown-Oculus Rift vs. HTC Vive]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>The Ars VR headset showdown-Oculus Rift vs. HTC Vive</h1><p>In our original reviews of the Oculus Rift and the HTC Vive, we tried very hard to examine these virtual reality systems on their own merits without constant comparisons to the competition. But no product exists in a vacuum. After years of buildup, we're now faced with two competitive, PC-tethered VR headsets hitting the market right next to each other.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/a473611978ca4931a0d74678d9cd4a6eaafdb8a9.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2016/04/the-ars-vr-headset-showdown-oculus-rift-vs-htc-vive/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">d7a538fc-7220-47dc-af69-dd7ecee0c9c4</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Aug 2016 09:55:05 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Why Tesla Will Destroy the Automobile Industry]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Why Tesla Will Destroy the Automobile Industry</h1><p>If there's an example of a company about to disruptively innovate an entire industry, it's Tesla. Partly, this is because of raw technology--Tesla's is clearly superior to that of its competitors. Partly, it's because Tesla has a more efficient business model. As Slate recently pointed out, Tesla bypasses value-subtracting dealer franchises and universally disliked car salespeople.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/967786c4c9a099ae3d4e342800c9901098d0268b.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.inc.com/geoffrey-james/why-tesla-will-destroy-the-automobile-industry.html?cid=sf01002&amp;sr_share=facebook</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">7ac7adf7-6685-4ea9-9717-c6fc44bb2c3b</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Aug 2016 09:55:05 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Impossible Project's first instant camera has an app with full manual controls]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>The Impossible Project's first instant camera has an app with full manual controls</h1><p>The Impossible Project is best known for keeping Polaroid's type 600 instant film format alive even after it was abandoned by the long-time camera maker in 2008. The company also refurbishes old Polaroid type 600 cameras in order to resell them.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/5c48b764b8e712eab67051afd16854e8d8ce70f6.png"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.theverge.com/2016/4/11/11409572/impossible-project-instant-camera-app-polaroid-format</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">f589600c-9f02-4628-b43b-3ab942731c2f</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Aug 2016 09:55:05 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[5 must-visit destinations in Patagonia for modern explorers]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>5 must-visit destinations in Patagonia for modern explorers</h1><p>Patagonia's 400,000 square miles are home to some of the most beautiful and diverse landscapes on the planet. It's an ideal destination for adventure seekers and one of our top destinations for travel in 2016. This expansive area of land, spread across southern Chile and Argentina, is too much to take in all at once.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/e6efb0a3ccb646f900a2bfa7ce773939dbc12ab9.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://mashable.com/2016/04/05/patagonia-adventure-travel/#GmuWjVf0GZqo</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2cc7847e-eba6-406a-bfed-fc024152dbb2</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Aug 2016 09:55:05 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mighty Audio's Portable Player]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Mighty Audio's Portable Player</h1><p>There's now a tech solution for those who are tired of having their phone tag along on fitness activities but don't want to give up their perfectly tailored Spotify playlists. Allowing runners, bikers and others to detach from the physical (and mental) weight of smartphones is Mighty Audio, which launches on Kickstarter today.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/7070b4eedc96d243e3c8c36783d47700e6d7d910.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.coolhunting.com/tech/mighty-kickstarter-portable-media-player-spotify-streaming</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">79ada39b-5fab-4f85-af17-fead1f092679</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Aug 2016 09:55:05 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Best Sailing Destinations in Europe | Travel Away]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Best Sailing Destinations in Europe | Travel Away</h1><p>Complementing its natural, cultural and historical richness, Europe prides itself with some of the world's most enchanting and glamorous sailing destinations. From the exclusive South of France to the fascinating old-meets-new jewel that is Turkey, the blue Mediterranean Sea is dotted with countless scenic islands and coasts, posh marinas, spellbinding natural wonders and precious little towns which, along with its perfect climate and sailing conditions, make this part of the world a true yacht lover's dream.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/9caa8f1b951888d39f6b06eb112bbe9b22e1a4ed.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://travelaway.me/sailing-destinations-europe/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">da8db244-01e9-4170-a948-2432b83e3df0</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Aug 2016 09:55:05 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[So Now We Know How C-3PO Got His Red Arm In The Force Awakens]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>So Now We Know How C-3PO Got His Red Arm In The Force Awakens</h1><p>Ladies and gentlemen, our global nightmare is over. After months-nearly five of them in fact-of waiting, Marvel's one-shot comic, revealing just why C-3PO has a red arm for most of The Force Awakens, is finally here. As bizarre as it may sound at first, the final product isn't half bad.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/ff7a99fdf22b973fd7d5ffe88bda91f4fec8e32d.png"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://io9.gizmodo.com/so-now-we-know-how-c-3po-got-his-red-arm-in-the-force-a-1770741572</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">5a048495-88ea-496b-b0cd-550591b3dc2a</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Aug 2016 09:55:05 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Experience a NASA Spacewalk Through the Lens of a GoPro Camera]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Experience a NASA Spacewalk Through the Lens of a GoPro Camera</h1><p>Want to see what it's like to "walk" around in space outside the International Space Station? NASA wants to show you. The agency recently strapped GoPro cameras onto two astronauts to capture the wonder of spacewalks from their perspective.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/d3d0f4303f6b7750f52857db8c393871f382887d.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://petapixel.com/2015/04/12/experience-a-nasa-spacewalk-through-the-lens-of-a-gopro-camera/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">6935a711-3a03-4f9b-b481-cb21f8baffb0</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Aug 2016 09:55:05 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>